

Rafał Baczyński-Sielaczek

Professional Goals

I'm master of sociology. After many years of working with people and for people I have chosen a new direction of professional development. This career path has interested me for quite a while. I believe that high quality is the bestselling point of services and products. Thanks to my diversified experience I have highly developed interpersonal skills and empathy, which help me see the bigger picture and function well within a team. My experience in Non Government Organisations has also equipped me with valuable tools, such as open-mindedness and adaptability.

In <u>Portfolio on GitHub</u> I would like to share my testing knowledge and exhibit my technical skills, which I gained during the testing course I have completed and through self-learning.

I write about my work experience and the tools I use in two articles: "Good practices in website testing" and "My testing tools".

Get in touch!



Mobile:

+48 796 110 204



Email:

r.baczynski.sielaczek@gmail.com



LinkedIn:

profile (clic to open)



GitHub:

website (clic to open)

Goals I'm working on:

1. Development of programming skills. In the near future I would like to develop as an automation tester. Purely manual testing limits the scope of testing.

The Direction: Java (IntelliJ IDEA Community Edition, Selenium WebDriver)

2. Developing skills related to Backend Testing - REST API, Postman. Fronted testing is not enough.

The Direction: REST API (Postman, Swagger)

3. Testing mobile and web applications. The internet is no longer stationary. Movement is an integral part of our lives. Applications and websites - must follow us. Current web testing will be very helpful in achieving this goal. The Direction: I started a course on creating automated tests for mobile applications at the user interface level. Creating tests using the Java programming language.

Experience



QA Specialist

Sobre Software House

Sep 2022 - actual, Żyrardów



Manual Tester

Sobre Software House

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022, Żyrardów



Manual Tester

Sii Poland

April 2021 - May 2022, Gdansk



Intern Manual Tester Sii Poland

Dec 2021 - March 2022, Gdansk

- Creating requirements for future functionalities;
- Coordinating UAT tests;
- Business specification analysis;
- Performing test cases;
- · Reporting defects in Jira;
- Consulting with developers and specialists
- Working in international environmen
- Supporting Test Lead for ongoing testing projects;
- Preparation of the test environment;
- Support in the process of preparing test plans;
- Writing test cases;
- Cooperation with Specialists in the implementation of projects;
- Debugging and reporting code bugs;
- Working on internal tools;
- Supporting developers in work on the code;
- Knowledge of ISTQB syllabus. Preparation for the ISTQB exam;
- Creating test cases using TestLlnk;
- Performing test cases;
- Reporting defects in Jira;
- Performing acceptance and exploration tests;



Senior Project Coordinator

Pomeranian Voivodeship Office in Gdansk/Caritas of the Archdiocese of Gdańsk





Business Development Specialist

National Institute of Silver Economy (KIGS)

ct 2016 - Mar 2018 Warsaw Metropolitan Area



Analyst, Migration Policy Programme

Institute of Public Affairs (IPA)

Feb 2015 - Jun 2016, Warsaw Metropolitan Area



Project Coordinator

Polish Humanitarian Action (PAH)

Sep 2010 - Mar 2015, Warsaw Metropolitan Are

Licenses & certifications

















Postman - testowanie REST API

Platforma Tester Oprogramowania, <u>www.testeroprogramowania.pl</u>

Kurs GIT dla początkujących

Platforma Tester Oprogramowania, <u>www.testeroprogramowania.pl</u>

Podstawy webdevelopmentu

Platforma Studiuję IT, <u>www.studiuje.it</u>

ISTQB® Foundation Level

STQB® - International Software Testing Qualifications Board

Become a Tester

Sii Poland

English for IT specialists, vol. 1

Udemy Oct 2021

Become a software tester from scratch

Udemy

PRINCE2® Foundation Certificate in Project Management

PeopleCert Oct 2017

Education



Master of Sociology

Nicolaus Copernicus University

Oct 2007

Specializations

Quality control Analytical skills Manual tests Accessibility (A11y)

Team management Interpersonal ability Teamwork

Languages Spoken

Polish

native

English

B2

Russian

• A1